(Raj:)Hey, I read
that someone invented a way
(Raj:)to convert your footsteps
into electromagnetic energy
(Raj:)so you can charge
your cell phone while walking.
(Leonard:)We had that idea years ago.
(Leonard:)How come we never
did anything with it?
(Howard:)Probably because we left the
diagram of it in the restaurant,
(Howard:)and none of us
wanted to walk back.
(Sheldon:)I know the real reason you never
made progress with that idea.
(Sheldon:)You thought of it
September 22, 2007.
(Sheldon:)Two days later, Penny moved in,
(Sheldon:)and so much blood rushed
to your genitals,
(Sheldon:)your brain became a ghost town.
(Leonard:)That's not what happened.
(Sheldon:)I remember it distinctly
(Sheldon:)because I had just
composed my annual poem
(Sheldon:)commemorating the anniversary
of Dr. Seuss's death.
(Howard:)No one wants
to hear it.
(Sheldon:)Why, die.
(Sheldon:)Why did he die?
(Sheldon:)Old, told.
(Sheldon:)I was told he was old.
(Leonard:)Penny is not the reason
I didn't pursue that idea.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
Since meeting her,
(Sheldon:)what have been
your greatest accomplishments?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Easy.
(Raj:)Sleeping with Penny.